Thirty-two years old. Virgin.
32歲，處女
I have not had sex even once.
從來沒有過所謂的“性經驗”
If you don't mind…
你願意的話…
Could you do it with me?
能和我做嗎？
Ouch!
好痛！
I'm sorry.
抱歉
This time…
這次…
Kagiya.
鍵谷
…I have to stop making mistakes.
…一定得確保不會把事情搞砸
Would you like to go for dinner together?
你不介意的話 下次要不要一起吃飯？
Yes.
好
He keeps his nose like…
他很常像這樣…
It was so fun being together.
在一起時明明很開心的
If I had experience,
如果我有經驗的話
would things have gone better with Kagiya?
是不是就能跟鍵谷更順利呢？
But because I made a move on him too quickly…
但也是因為我突然上前…
Kagiya?
鍵谷？
I'm sorry.
對不起
Wait, Kagiya!
等一下，鍵谷
Because I was too aggressive,
因為我太主動了
he must have been put him off.
所以他退縮了吧？
I don't want it to end yet.
我還不想結束
I need to talk to him again.
我想再跟鍵谷說一次話
SHINTA FUJIMOTO YOUNGEST EVER TO COMPETE IN THE OSHO TITLE MATCH
（藤本新太二冠 王將戰最年輕的選手）
MAIKO KOSAKA INCOMING CALL
（香坂麻衣子來電）
He never called back…
那之後，他也沒再打回來
KAGIYA I CALLED YOU YESTERDAY
（鍵谷，我昨天打給你）
What if he ignores my texts too?
要是他連訊息都不看呢？
That would definitely mean the end.
那就真的結束了
There's no coming back from that.
再也回不去了
Oh, you're from Eikou.
喔，榮光的人員
Are you here for maintenance?
你來定期維修嗎？
Kagiya?
鍵谷？
-No, not maintenance. -Oh, I see.
-不，不是定期維修 -是喔
What brings you here then?
那怎麼會過來呢？
To deliver toner.
我是來送碳粉的
It's not him.
不是他
Thank you.
謝謝
Maybe he doesn't want to see me so he asked for a transfer.
該不會是因為不想見到我 所以變更了負責區域…
Or what?
之類的？
Thank you.
謝謝
Did he already end things?
他已經決定結束了嗎？
Kosaka knows nothing about me.
香坂根本不了解我
…by defeating Motojima Akio
…擊敗本島昭夫
in the opening match of the Osho Title Tournament League.
取得歷史性的29連勝
Shinta Fujimoto back in January of this year…
藤本新太在今年1月回歸…
Kagiya?
鍵谷？
I'm sorry.
對不起
Wait--
等一下…
In 1958…
在1958年…
I'm running away from everything.
我逃離了一切
Check.
將軍
I give up.
我認輸了
That's a good move.
真是出色的一步
Well played.
下得很好
Kagiya, you're good at this.
鍵谷，你很強呢
I resign.
我輸了
Someone like me
這樣的我
should have never even tried to be with someone.
要跟別人在一起，本來就是個錯誤
Wow!
哇！
That looks so good on you, Miyuki.
真適合你耶，美由紀
I know.
我知道
Oh, please.
真是的
Well, it actually suits you, so it's fine.
不過真的很適合你，所以沒關係
Ms. Misono seems different somehow since her day off.
味園小姐休假後感覺變得不太一樣了
Then hurry back to your own work.
那就趕快回去做自己的工作
How nice…
真好
I should also stop overthinking and get back to work.
我也別再胡思亂想，專心工作吧
Um, Ms. Misono?
味園小姐
Is there anything I can help with?
有什麼我可以幫忙的嗎？
What?
什麼？
Really?
這樣啊
Take care of this, then.
那這些就麻煩你了
Sorry for making you help.
抱歉，要麻煩你幫忙
No, that's what I'm here for as a temp.
不會，就是因為這樣 才需要派遣人員嘛
Shall we get started then?
那我們從這邊開始吧？
Yes.
好
Huh, is it an employee interview?
喔，是員工訪談啊
Ah, this person is from Musashi-Koyama. Same as me.
這個人也住在武藏小山，跟我一樣
Kosaka, do you live alone?
香坂，你一個人住嗎？
Uh, yeah.
呃，對啊
Being independent is so cool.
獨立生活好酷喔
I'm still living at my parents' house at 26.
我雖然26歲了，但還是住在老家
But you live in Musashi-Koyama, right? I'm jealous.
但是你住在武藏小山吧？我很羨慕呢
No, I'm just mooching off my parents.
不，我只是靠父母而已啦
She definitely qualifies as the pretty type.
就類型來說，她算是漂亮的吧
I bet she's popular,
一定很受歡迎
and she probably has a fairly handsome, high-caliber boyfriend.
可能還有個帥氣、條件又好的男友吧
Let's divide it into paragraphs to avoid mistakes.
我們把內容分段比較不會出錯
Yes.
好
They say lookism isn't good,
大家總說外表不重要
but usually handsome guys choose beautiful women,
但基本上帥哥就會選美女
and beautiful women choose handsome guys.
美女也會選帥哥
So I figured someone as ugly as me would never get chosen.
所以我覺得 不會有人想選像我這樣的醜女
But then I tried a casual app…
但當我試著用了交友軟體後…
IT'S A MATCH!
（配對成功）
Well, it didn't continue after that, though.
只是就沒有後續了呢
What?
什麼？
Ah, no, it's nothing.
啊，沒有，沒什麼
Ah, this part needs a prolonged sound mark, right?
這邊需要延長記號，對吧？
Ah, yeah, I guess.
對，應該要
-Okay, let me fix it. -Alright, thanks.
-好，那我修正了 -好，謝謝
Hey.
你好
Except for Keita.
就只有啓太了
He's the only one who wanted to meet again.
他是交友軟體上 唯一想再見我一次的人
It's not raining.
外面沒下雨
The forecast said rain.
氣象預報說會下的說
Could it be that he likes me?
難道他喜歡我嗎？
Hmm? What?
嗯？什麼？
Oh! D.Pool!
喔，是D.Pool！
I wanted it after we talked about it.
上次聊過後，我就想買了
How nice. It's such an emotional album.
好好喔，那張專輯很動人吧？
The second track is amazing, right?
第二首超棒的，對吧？
The one that starts with the piano? That one is so good.
開頭是鋼琴的那首？ 我懂，那首超棒的
I thought you'd say that, Ms. Ren.
我就知道蓮小姐會這麼說
You can call me "Ren."
叫我蓮就可以了
You're a year older than me after all.
畢竟你還比我大一歲
Ah… then, Ren it is.
這樣啊，那就叫蓮吧
Yeah.
嗯
I'm having fun, but…
雖然很開心，但是…
He's ugly.
他實在很醜
I guess he's also only seeing me because he can't find anyone else.
我想他也是找不到其他人 才會找我的吧
Um…
哎呀
My nails are a mess.
我的指甲都剝落了
Maybe I should find a hobby.
是不是該培養嗜好呢？
Then maybe I can forget about Kagiya.
也許這樣就能忘掉鍵谷的事情
POTTERY LESSONS
（陶藝教室）
HANDICRAFT
（手工藝課程）
Thinking about it,
回想起來
all I know about Kagiya is his name and job.
我只知道鍵谷的名字和工作
Where he lives, if he likes sweets,
他住在哪裡、喜不喜歡甜食
whether he's a cat person or a dog person, nothing…
他是貓派或是狗派，什麼都…
We should have talked more about those kind of things.
要是有多聊聊這些事情就好了
DENKIYA HALL
（電氣屋廳堂）
He wouldn't be here, would he?
鍵谷不在…吧？
Here's the menu.
請參考菜單
Oh, it's you.
喔，之前的那位
Hello.
你好
Do you like games?
你喜歡遊戲嗎？
I had fun last time, so I came again.
之前玩得很開心，所以想再來一次
Coffee, please.
請給我咖啡
Yes.
好的
Alright, let's do this.
好，來玩吧
Yes!
好！
For some reason…
怎麼回事？
It's not really fun.
感覺沒那麼開心
Right…
原來如此
It was fun because he was there with me.
是因為有鍵谷在，所以才那麼開心
DENKIYA HALL
（電氣屋廳堂）
I'm sorry for making you work overtime.
小平，不好意思讓你加班了
Not at all. It just means I earn that much more.
不會啦，加班我也能賺更多
Don't you have any date plans or something?
香坂你沒有預訂要約會之類的嗎？
Huh, a date?
咦？約會？
Not at all.
沒有啊
What's your type?
你喜歡的類型是什麼？
Huh? Me?
呃，我嗎？
Yes.
對啊
You seem like the type to go for high-caliber.
感覺你喜歡條件很好的類型
Hmm, my type…
嗯…類型啊
Someone fun, I guess.
有趣的人吧
Huh?
咦？
Uh, someone fun?
有趣的人？
Yeah.
對
Someone who's fun to be with.
在一起時會很開心的人
I want someone who makes me smile.
能夠自然而然讓我微笑的人
What about you?
你呢？
Someone handsome.
帥哥吧
That was fast.
回答得真快
PRINT
（列印）
Here, the key to the storage room.
給你，這是倉庫的鑰匙
T-Thank you.
謝謝
I'll leave the rest to you.
麻煩你了
Hello.
辛苦了
This… Right?
這是…你的嗎？
Yes.
對
I thought maybe you had been transferred.
那個，我以為你換負責區域了
It's no good. I don't know what else to say.
果然不行，不知道還能再說些什麼
Kosaka. I finished.
香坂，我做完了
Thank you, you were a great help.
謝謝，幫大忙了
Then, I'll go ahead…
那我就先…
Sorry, I'll leave first.
不好意思，我先走了
Hmm?
什麼狀況？
She looked sad.
香坂她…看起來很難過
That's Pac-Man, right?
這是《小精靈》吧？
I can't get past level eight.
我只能過到第八關
I got to 21.
我可以過到21關
Wow, really?
哇，好厲害
Can I come with you?
我可以一起去嗎？
What?
什麼？
Wow! It's really Pac-Man!
哇，真的是《小精靈》耶
You're so good at it!
好強
It's so good.
好好喝
What am I doing?
我在做什麼啊？
Involving her in my own issues…
把不相干的香坂扯進自己的問題裡
I hoped to run into him somewhere.
本來還期待著可以偶然碰到面
But then when we finally did meet…
不過真的見面之後
It was hopeless.
還是沒辦法
Once you make a mistake, you can't go back.
果然出了一次錯 就再也不可能恢復了
I guess Kagiya and I…
我和鍵谷已經…
Kosaka!
香坂！
Kagiya?
鍵谷？
What happened?
怎麼了？
I'm sorry.
對不起
I'm weirding you out, aren't I?
我嚇到你了吧？
I'll go home.
我還是回去好了
Wait, please.
請等一下
I'm sorry about the other day.
之前的事情，我很抱歉
Huh?
什麼？
For coming on so strong.
強迫你做那些事
It must have grossed you out.
你一定覺得很不舒服吧？
I'm truly sorry.
真的很抱歉
No,
不
not at all.
完全不會
Huh?
咦？
It's my fault.
是我不好
That was…
那是…
my problem.
我的問題
"My problem"?
“我的問題”？
I'll tell you everything.
我會向你好好說明一切的
I haven't moved forward at all since.
我從那之後就完全無法前進
Even if it's fun, if he's not handsome…
雖然很有趣，但不是帥哥果然不行
They're probably wondering why he's with someone as ugly as me.
別人會覺得為何要 和我這種醜女在一起吧？
I don't want to let go yet either.
我也還不想放開
I want to do more with him.
我想和鍵谷多做一點